Tamer Mustafa Samara

Profession : Administrative Assistant Phone : 0772534984 / 0790941348

Address : Nazzal Area — opposite to Al Shaima'a Banqueting Halls.

Email : tamer yaseen2000@yahoo.com



I have 14 years of experience in office administration. I have a certificate of Functional Secretariat. I do possess extensive expertise in Typing, Correspondence, MS Office and office administration practice in general. I would like to start a new career as **Administrative Assistant** or any related job in a successful and growing organization.

Skills

- Excellent communications skills.
- Independently working person.
- Fast learner.
- Information searching.
- Writing (reporting) skills.
- Editing and proofreading of documents.
- Excellent Microsoft Office skills: Word Excel and Outlook.
- Filing skills.
- Excellent typing skills.
- Excellent supervising and following up skills.

Work History

Feb. 2024 – Present

Sales Team's Assistant / Online (part time) job

Detroit for Training & Consulting Est.

Responsibilities:

- Searching, recommending and recording of potential clients.
- Assisting in following up the daily activities and work progress of sales team.
- Working on adding a direct tutoring class to the establishment.

Nov. 2015 – Jan. 2024

Administrative Assistant

Al Bunnia Group

Responsibilities:

- Providing all secretarial and administrative services to various departments.
- Providing secretarial and administrative assistance to G.M.'s Office.
- Monitor and recording the attendance of employees.
- Perform software and hard copy filing.
- Receiving work reports from employees on daily basis.
- General typing of documents and official letters.
- Prepare and reserving meeting rooms when necessary; and give any needed assistance for attendees.
- Handling the petty cash and purchasing of stationery.
- Supervising and monitoring work on security guards, cleaning boys, drivers and following up on maintenance matters.

Jan. 2012 – July. 2015

Office Secretary & Assistant for Sales Team

Sariat Al Urdon Investment and Development

Responsibilities:

- Reminding of the appointments of the General Manager.
- Working with Sales Team in : filing, communications, and following up due installments.
- General routine work of: typing, filing, faxing, photocopying and phone calls

Sept. 2009 - April. 2011

Office Manager & Public Relations Employee

Geotechnical & Environmental Solutions Co.

Responsibilities:

- General supervising of office's issues.
- General routine work of: typing letters and correspondence, e-mail communications, filing, phone calls and faxing.

- Preparing offers, marketing materials and post.
- Prepare documentation for Engineers work and needs.
- Performing delivery of post, offers, samples etc.. to different parties.
- Performing money deposits.
- Handling the petty cash, stationary, and monthly bills.

Jan. 2008 – May. 2009

Administrative Assistant / in Technical Unit

INTRACOM Jordan

Responsibilities:

- General supervising of office's issues.
- Give assistance to Technical Unit Manager and Team Leaders with different secretariat services.
- Monitor attendance of employees, and recording leaves, vacations, morning delays, over time.
- Receiving work reports from employees on daily basis (and recorded within Excel sheets).

Personal Information

Date of Birth : 31/8/1978 (Tulkarm City — Palestine)

Nationality : Jordanian

Marital Status: Married

Education

1995 – 1996 High School Certificate (Commercial Section)

Imam Ali Bin Abi Taleb Secondary School

1996 – 1997 Functional Secretariat Course (an office administration course)

Sight and Sound Educational Centre.